Finding Aid for Fred Newton Scott papers, 1860-1931
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Fred Newton Scott papers 1860-1931
Scott, Fred Newton
1 oversize folders
3 linear feet
86145 Aa 2; Ac
Professor of rhetoric and journalism at University of Michigan. Correspondence concerning his professional activities, particularly his interest in linguistics and English language and speech, and papers, 1917-1918, concerning war issues course at the University, manuscripts of articles and speeches, diary, 1903-1909, day-books, 1903-1922, and miscellaneous notebooks and journals; also photographs.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The bulk of the collection was the gift of Mrs. Fred Newton Scott (donor no. 1283 ) and came to the library in 1940-1941.
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Fred Newton Scott was born in Terre Haute, Indiana, in 1860, but the family later moved to Battle Creek, Michigan, where he attended local schools before entering the University of Michigan. After completing his education at the university, Scott (B.A. 1884, M.A. 1888, PH.D. 1889) began a long and distinguished career on the faculty of the university. His interest in upholding high standards of English usage and the teaching of sound writing principles led to the founding of the Department of Rhetoric in 1903, which he headed until his retirement in 1927.
As early as 1890-91 he had offered a course in "Rapid Writing". This developed into Course 13, "Newspaper Writing; Theory and Practice," offered in the new department, and marks the beginning of the study of journalism at the University of Michigan and in the nation. Under his leadership the department became a leader in the teaching of creative writing, journalism, and criticism.
When, in 1897, the Board of Regents established a university news service for the purpose of getting out news of university activities to the people of the state, Scott was appointed University News Editor. Under his direction, the special news section in the Michigan Alumnus was reprinted and distributed to state newspaper editors and legislators. Thus began the university's first news service program.
From 1903 to 1927, Scott was chairman of the Board in Control of Student Publications and was credited with helping many generations of student editors, some of whom went on to distinguished careers as newspaper editors and publishers.
Fred N. Scott's professional activities were national and international in scope. He was a member of the North Central Association and the American Association of Teachers of Journalism, and served as president of the National Council of Teachers of English and of the Modern Language Association. He was also a member of the English Association of Great Britain and actively worked to organize an American branch of the Society for Pure English.
After his retirement in 1927, Scott and his second wife, Georgia Jackson (a former student), moved to Tucson, Arizona. Retirement did not diminish his interest in promoting good English usage. He actively lent support to the teaching of rhetoric at the University of Arizona and gave the department there $2,000 to fund a student prize for excellence in writing.
In the spring of 1930 the University of Michigan Board of Regents voted to grant Scott an honorary degree. However, his failing health did not permit him to travel and he had to decline the honor, as the degree is not granted in absentia. He died on May 29, 1931.
The Fred Newton Scott collection includes correspondence, drafts of articles and reviews, diaries, daybooks, some personal materials, and photographs.
The correspondence is the core of the collection, consisting mainly of incoming letters to Scott from friends, colleagues, students, publishers, editors, authors, and learned societies. The letters deal mainly with literary and language questions and with Scott's lecture engagements, book reviewing, and other writings. The correspondence, arranged chronologically, is between Scott and four categories of individuals: Students; Journalists and publishers; Professional associates; and University colleagues and other.
I. Students
The wide-ranging influence of Scott's philosophy and teaching is amply illustrated through letters from his former students. They kept him informed of how they were putting his principles into practice as journalists or in academic teaching, and sought his advice on further developments in their work. The accomplishments of women students who had studied with him are particularly noteworthy. Gertrude Buck, whose dissertation on metaphor was considered a definitive study at the time, became a professor at Vassar College. In 1898, she had received the first Ph.D. in Rhetoric awarded by the University of Michigan. Other women students who went on to distinguished careers included Marjorie Nicolson, English professor and dean of Smith College; Helen Mahin, professor of journalism, University of Kansas; Ada Snell, Wellesley College; and Phyllis Povah Drayton, actress. Georgia Jackson was one of the first women to serve on the editorial staff of The American Boy magazine and later became editor of the Literary Digest. Other students of Scott were Frank Mitchell, Katherine Reed, Alice D. Snyder, Katherine Taylor, and Joseph M. Thomas.
Perhaps the most locally prominent among men graduates was Lee A. White who became editor of The Detroit News. Scott also numbered among his accomplished students, Avery Hopwood, playwright and donor of the Hopwood prizes; Wilfred B. Shaw, author and editor, and Director of Alumni Relations at the University of Michigan; Paul Osborn, playwright; Edgar A. and Paul Scott Mowrer, journalists; Joseph Thomas, Dean of the Senior College, University of Minnesota; James O. Bennett, journalist, The Chicago Tribune and Walter A. Donnelly, editor and Director of the University of Michigan Press.
II. Journalists and Publishers
As Scott developed courses in journalism he called on editors and publishers, some of whom had been his students, to lecture on the practical side of newspaper work. Much of this correspondence concerns arrangements for, and contents and evaluations of, these lectures. Since he was also concerned with improving journalistic writing, some letters deal with projects he undertook in cooperation with editors to raise the standards and styles of reportorial work. These professionals included James O. Bennett, Edmund Booth, George Booth, Frank Cobb, J.W. Cunliffe, Willard B. Gore, W.W. Harris, Roy Howard, Frank G. Kane, James M. Lee, Louis Ling, Milton A. McRae, C.M. Marstow, Robert Mountsier, Edgar Ansel Mowrer, Paul Scott Mowrer, Chases S. Osborn, E.G. Pipp, Arthur C. Pound, James Schermerhorn, James E. Scripps, Edwin E. Slosson, and Lee A. White.
III. Professional associates
Many of the letters in F. N. Scott's papers deal with his work on the National Council of Teachers of English and other professional organizations in which he played an active role. These are scattered throughout the collection but are not listed here. The largest amount of correspondence is that related to his interest in setting up an academy for the improvement of the English language. A British organization, the Society for Pure English, had been founded in 1913. In early 1922, a committee was organized, with Scott as chairman, to work with a British committee consisting of Robert Bridges, Henry Newbolt, and J. Dover Wilson, to form an international academy of English. The members of the American committee were: Henry Seidel Canby, Charles M. Gayley, Charles H. Grandgent, John L. Lowes, and John M. Manley. Other correspondents within organizations with whom Scott corresponded included John W. Bright, C.G. Hoag, F.P. Keppel, and Louise Pound. There also letters exchanged with Henry Ford.
IV. University colleagues and others
Included here are letters of Professor Thomas E. Rankin dealing with departmental affairs when he was acting chairman of the department in Scott's absence, and also his reactions to the later merging of the department with the Department of English. Aside from departmental and university concerns, the collection includes extensive correspondence with Jean Paul Slusser who became director of the Museum of Art following a long career teaching design and painting at the university. There is also correspondence with Regent Lucius Hubbard who shared Scott's interest in good English usage and in rare books. In addition, Scott was attracted to the health teachings of John Harvey Kellogg, stayed at his sanitarium in Battle Creek, and exchanged letters with him regarding his health regimen. Other correspondents include John Effinger, Peter Monro Jack, Clarence Cook Little, and Charles E. Whitman.
Subjects:
Journalists--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Language and languages.; Modern Language Association.; American newspapers.; Scott, Fred Newton, 1860-1931.; University of Michigan. Dept. of Journalism.; University of Michigan. Dept. of Rhetoric.; University of Michigan--Faculty.; University of Michigan--Football.; World War, 1914-1918--Education and the war.; World War, 1914-1918--Michigan--Ann Arbor.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Dwellings.; Dwellings--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Scott, Fred Newton, 1860-1931.
Contributors:
Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916.; Babbitt, Irving, 1865-1933.; Baker, Ray Stannard, 1870-1946.; Bishop, William Warner, 1871-1955.; Booth, Edmund Wood, 1866-1927.; Booth, George G. (George Gough), b. 1864.; Bridges, Robert Seymour, 1844-1930.; Bryant, John Howard, 1807-1902.; Canby, Henry Seidel, 1878-1961.; Catlin, George B. (George Byron), 1857-1934.; Cobb, Frank Irving, 1869-1923.; Cunliffe, John William, 1865-1946.; Denney, Joseph Villiers, 1862-1935.; Detroit Municipal League.; Dewey, John, 1859-1952.; Douglas, Lloyd C. (Lloyd Cassel), 1877-1951.; Effinger, John Robert, 1869-1933.; Ford, Henry, 1863-1947.; Grant, Claudius Buchanan, 1835-1921.; Guest, Edgar A. (Edgar Albert), 1881-1959.; Harriman, Karl Edwin, 1875-1935.; Hopwood, Avery, 1882-1928.; Hubbard, Lucius L. (Lucius Lee), 1849-1933.; Jordan, David Starr, 1851-1931.; Kahn, Albert, 1869-1942.; Kellogg, John Harvey, 1852-1943.; Kelsey, Francis W. (Francis Willey), 1858-1927.; Knox, Frank, 1874-1944.; Koch, Theodore Wesley, 1871-1941.; Little, Clarence C. (Clarence Cook), b. 1888.; Miller, Edwin Lillie, 1868-1934.; Murfin, James Orin, 1875-1940.; Nevins, Allan, 1890-1971.; Newbolt, Henry John, 1862-1938.; Osborn, Chase S. (Chase Salmon), b. 1860.; Pattengill, Albert Henderson, 1842-1906.; Perry, Stuart Hoffman, 1874-1957.; Phelps, William Lyon, 1865-1943.; Pound, Arthur, 1884-1966.; Scripps, James E. (James Edmund), 1835-1906.; Shelley, Rebecca, 1887-1984.; Slosson, Edwin Emery, 1865-1929.; Society for Pure English.; Staebler, Neil, 1905-2000; Stoddard, Francis Hovey, 1847-1936.; Trueblood, Thomas C. (Thomas Clarkson), 1856-1951.; Wenley, R. M. (Robert Mark), 1861-1929.; White, Lee A., b. 1886.; Wilcox, Delos F. (Delos Franklin), 1873-1928.
Genre Terms:
Diaries.; Photographs.; Silhouettes.
- Correspondence
  - 1882-1923, 31 folders (Box 1)
  - 1924-1931 undated, 11 folders (Box 2)
- Articles and reviews, 5 folders
  (microfilm copy available)
  - Miscellaneous 1
    - Biography of Miss Harriet M. Scott (Box 2)
    - Advertising English (Box 2)
    - An analogy (Box 2)
    - The story of philosophy (Box 2)
    - The figurative element in grammatical terminology (Box 2)
    - Improving the English of America (Box 2)
    - Differences between English and American vernacular (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous 2
    - Untitled (Box 2)
    - Review of Cunliffe's English literature during the last half century (Box 2)
    - Rhetorica rediviva (Box 2)
    - Notes on "Thanatopsis" (Box 2)
    - The aims and the field of graduate study (Box 2)
    - Medicated drama (Box 2)
    - How to read the newspapers (Box 2)
    - Obverse: in memory of one who died for freedom and humanity (Box 2)
    - Books that wear and books that wear out (Box 2)
    - Some editorial vices (Box 2)
    - Untitled (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous 3
    - Rhetoric (Box 2)
    - Serendipity (Box 2)
    - Untitled (Box 2)
    - An anchor to windward (Box 2)
    - Untitled (Box 2)
    - How to bring pressure or stimulus to bear upon the inert (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous 4
    - Notes on Keats' Isabella (Box 2)
    - Prose rhythm (Box 2)
    - The origin of literary species (Box 2)
    - Speech 1929 (Box 2)
    - Standard of taste (Box 2)
    - Training for journalism (Box 2)
    - Deathless lines (Box 2)
    - Arthur Graham Hall: a memorial (Box 2)
    - The organization of the speech community (Box 2)
    - Letter to the editor Michigan Daily (Box 2)
    - Some editorial vices (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous 5
    - Newspaper English (Box 2)
    - The poetic work of art in contrast to the prosaic (Box 2)
    - Questions of good English (Box 2)
    - Simplified spelling and simplified pronunciation (Box 2)
    - Simplified spelling for business men (Box 2)
    - Questions of good English (Box 2)
    - The use of superfluous words (Box 2)
    - The huge pink face (Box 2)
    - The coming freedom (Box 2)
    - The art of dictation (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous papers
  - War issues course at the University of Michigan 1917-1918 (Box 2)
  - Programs, invitations, etc. (Box 2)
  - Genealogical and biographical material (Box 2)
  - Miscellanea (Box 2)
  - Mrs. F.N. Scott papers 1916-1939, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - University of Michigan Senate Memorial to F.N. Scott (Box 2)
  - Thesis 1889 "Italian Critics of the Renaissance" (Box 2)
  - Notes for Rhetoric 168 course (Box 2)
  - Parody entitled, "Mr. Dooley among the Professors" (Box 2)
    (found in book, Lady in the Lake by Sir Walter Scott)
  - Photographs: portraits and photographs of Scott engaged in professional activity (Box 2)
- Diaries
  - October 1903-December 1904 (Box 3)
  - January-December 1905 (Box 3)
  - December 1905-December 1906 (Box 3)
  - February-December 1907 (Box 3)
  - January-June 1908 (Box 3)
  - April-December 1909 (Box 3)
- Day-books
  - 1903-1905 (Box 3)
  - 1905-1908 (Box 3)
  - 1909-1911 (Box 3)
  - 1911-1916 (Box 3)
  - 1920-1922 (Box 3)
  - 1903-1911 (Box 3)
    (typescript selections)
  - Miscellaneous notebooks and journals (Box 3)
Selective Index to Correspondents
Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916.
Aug. 1, 1889, Feb. 22, 1915
Babbitt, Irving, 1865-1933.
1919
Baker, Ray Stannard, 1870-1946.
Feb. 4, 1911, Dec. 20, 1928
Bennett, James O.
July 22, 1909
Bishop, William Warner, 1871-1955.
Nov. 4, 1927, July 5, 1928
Booth, Edmund Wood, 1866-1927.
Mar. 17 & 26, 1910, May 3 & 10, 1910, Oct. 25, 1910, Nov. 17, 1910, Feb. 25, 1910, Feb. 25, 1915
Booth, George G. (George Gough), b. 1864.
Mar. 10, 1910, Mar. 11, 1910
Bridges, Robert Seymour, 1844-1930.
1919, Apr. 18, 1922, May 15 & 26, 1922, June 17, 1922, Oct. ?, 1922, June 8, 1923, Aug. 28, 1923, Oct. 30, 1923, Nov. 23, 1923, July 17, 1924, Aug. 29, 1924, Sept. 9, 1924, Oct. 19 & 17, 1924, Nov. 18, 1924
Jan. 17, 1925, Feb. 21, 1925, June 13 & 29, 1925, May 2, 1926, June 3, 27 & 30, 1926, July 20, 1927, Aug. 25, 1927, 1928
Bright, John W.
Nov. 24, 1922, Dec. 17, 1922, Jan. 24, 1923
Bryant, John Howard, 1807-1902.
May 5, 1896
Buck, Gertrude
Apr. 22, 1905, Oct. 28, 1909, Feb. 3, 1910, Mar. 5, 1910, Apr. 23, 1910, June 11, 1910, Nov. 2, 1910, June 7, 1912, July 1, 1912, Oct. 2, 1912, Oct. 9, 1912, Oct. 14, 1912, Oct. 19, 1912, Nov. 12, 1912, Dec. 9 & 12, 1912
Jan. 6, 1913, Feb. 22, 1913, Mar. 11, 1913, Apr. 3, 1913, Oct. 11, 1913, Oct. 18, 1913, Dec. 3, 1913, Jan. 24, 1914, Mar. 30, 1914, Oct. 15, 1914, Dec. 9, 1914, Feb. 5, 1919, Oct. 25, 1919
Canby, Henry Seidel, 1878-1961.
Dec. 3, 1911, Jan. 1, 1916, July 4, 1922, Aug. 15, 1923, Oct. 29, 1923, July 21, 1924, Aug. 5, 8, 24 & 28, 1924, Nov., plan of organization, 1924
Jan. 20, 1925, Apr. 13, 21 & 22, 1925, May 5, 11, 20 & 27, 1925, Aug. 4, 1925, Oct. 28, 1925, May 26, 1926, June 7, 1926, Nov. 4, 1926, Dec. 23, 1927, Jan. 18, 1928, Feb. 18, 1928
Cobb, Frank Irving, 1869-1923.
Jan. 6 & 23, 1912, Apr. 3, 1915
Cunliffe, John William, 1865-1946.
Jan. 15, 1910, Feb. 12, 1910, Mar. 24, 1913, Apr. 9, 1913
Denney, Joseph Villiers, 1862-1935.
Sept. 12, 1907, May 28, 1908, 1910, Oct. 30, 1912, Mar. 1, 1919, May 30, 1919, June 3, 1919, July 20, 1921, Jan. 31, 1923
Detroit Municipal League
July 20, 1911
Dewey, John, 1859-1952.
Nov. 5, 1917, July 6, 1918, Aug. 22, 1929
Douglas, Lloyd C. (Lloyd Cassel), 1877-1951.
Undated
Effinger, John R. (John Robert), 1869-1933.
Nov. 12, 1923, Oct. 2, 1926, Apr. 14, 1927, May 10, 1927, Aug. 14, 1927
Ford, Henry, 1863-1947.
Nov. 27, 1915, Aug. 17, 1924, Sept. 15, 1924, Sept. 17, 1924, Nov. 11, 1924
Gore, Willard B.
May 18, 1910
Grandgent, Charles H.
June 5, 1922, Nov. 23, 1922, Jan. 22, 1923
Grant, Claudius Buchanan, 1835-1921.
Dec. 1904
Guest, Edgar A. (Edgar Albert), 1881-1959.
May 28, 1917
Harriman, Karl Edwin, 1875-1935.
Sept. 6, 1905, Oct. 16, 1907, Nov. 9, 1907, May 1925, Mar. 14, 1928
Harris, W. W.
Dec. 2, 1915
Hoag, C. G.
Mar. 17, 23, 1922, May 19 & 31, 1922, June 6, 1922, Dec. 30, 1922, Jan. 23, 1923, May 7 & 21, 1923, Nov. 13, 1923, Apr. 17, 1924, June 6, 1924, Oct. 20 & 29, 1924
Apr. 13, 17 & 27, 1925, June 5, 1925, Nov. 4, 1925, Jan. 18, 1926, Apr. 16, 17 & 30, 1926, May 8, 15 & 28, 1926, June 2 & 8, 1926, Sept. 17, 1926, Apr. 22, 1927, May 10, 1927
Hopwood, Avery, 1882-1928.
Sept. 29, 1907
Howard, Roy.
Mar. 24, 1913, Apr. 9, 1913
Hubbard, Lucius L. (Lucius Lee), 1849-1933
Sept. 22, 1916, May 10, 1917, July 1 & 5, 1919, Aug. 23 & 27, 1919, Sept. 10, 1919, Oct. 9, 1919, Jan. 26, 1920, Apr. 11, 12 & 16, 1920, Dec. 12, 1920, Mar. 28, 1922, Apr. 9, 1927, July 28, 1929
Jack, Peter Monro
Apr. 2, 1928
Jackson, Georgia
Nov. 1, 1912, Dec. 8 & 16, 1915, Jan. 6, 1916, Mar. 7, 1916, May 2, 1916, June 2 & 16, 1916, Aug. 2 & 25, 1916, Dec. 9, 23 & 31, 1916, Jan. 12, 1917, May 14, 23 & 31, 1917, June 19, 1917, Aug. 1 1917, Oct. 23, 1917, Dec. 5 & 17, 1917
Jan. 17, 1918, Mar. 26, 1918, Apr. 6, 1918, June 3 & 8, 1918, Oct. 3, 1918, Jan. 9 & 28, 1919, Apr. 5, 1919, May 7, 1919, July 2 & 10, 1919, Oct. 16, 18, 29 & 31, 1919, Dec. 5 & 11, 1919
Jan. 11, 1920, Mar. 17, 1920, Apr. 27, 1920, May 1, 1920, June 3, 1920, Dec. 11, 1920, June 10, 1921, July 8, 1921, Sept. 16, 1921, Nov. 7, 1921, Dec. 7, 1921
Jordan, David Starr, 1851-1931.
May 26, 1903
Kahn, Albert, 1869-1942.
1916
Kane, Frank G.
Oct. 13, 1912, Sept. 7, 1913, Oct. 11, 1919
Kellogg, John Harvey, 1852-1943.
Apr. 11, 1910, June 7, 1910, Sept. 30, 1912, Apr. 30, 1913, May 8, 1913, June 25, 1913, Dec. 2, 1914, Sept. 27, 1918, Mar. 31, 1922, Apr. 5, 1922, Nov. 18 & 24, 1922
May 16 & 28, 1923, Oct. 19, 1923, Apr. 29, 1926, May 24, 1926, Mar. 2, 1927, Sept. 7, 1929, Oct. 1929
Kelsey, Francis W. (Francis Willey), 1858-1927.
Aug. 10, 1920, Oct. 9, 1925
Keppel, F. P.
Dec. 30, 1923
Knox, Frank, 1874-1944.
July 29, 1910, Aug. 11, 1910
Koch, Theodore Wesley, 1871-1941.
Dec. 1921
Lee, James M.
Feb. 21, 1914
Ling, Louis.
May 24, 1911
Little, Clarence C. (Clarence Cook), b. 1888.
June 18, 1926, July 12, 1926, Nov. 23, 1926, Dec. 1, 1926 (Scott's letter of resignation), 1927
Lowes, John L.
June 9, 1922, Nov. 26, 1922, Dec. 25, 1922, July 29, 1923, Aug. 8 & 13, 1924, Sept. 30, 1924, Jan. 15, 1925
McRae, Milton A.
Sept. 6, 1910, Jan. 13 & 18, 1911, Mar. 31, 1913
Mahin, Helen D.
Oct. 20, 1918, Dec. 18, 1925, Aug. 24, 1930
Manly, John M.
June 6, 1922, Dec. 1, 1922, Aug. 1, 1923, Aug. 5 & 28, 1924, Sept. 30, 1924, Oct. 2 & 29, 1924, Nov. 5, 1924, Apr. 14, 1925
Marstow, C. M.
Mar. 11, 1913
Miller, Edwin Lillie, 1868-1934.
Mar. 9, 1910, June 12, 1910, Aug. 27, 1910
Mitchell, Frank
Nov. 7, 1922, Jan. 24, 1923, May 1, 1923, Nov. 8, 1923, Nov. 29, 1923, Feb. 21, 1924, Good Friday, 1924, May 17, 1924, July 17, 1924, Apr. 26, 1925, June 20, 1925, Aug. 14, 1925, Oct. 4, 1925, Jan. 6, 1926, June 4, 1926, Oct. 1, 1926, Apr. 19, 1929
Mountsier, Robert.
Mar. 11, 1913
Mowrer, Edgar Ansel.
July 15, 1912, Mar. 12, 1917
Mowrer, Paul Scott.
Sept. 25, 1911, Oct. 25, 1911, Jan. 24, 1918, Sept. 11, 1918, Apr. 29, 1925
Murfin, James Orin, 1875-1940.
Nov. 14, 1918
Nevins, Allan, 1890-1971.
Feb. 5, 1923, Mar. 31, 1923
Newbolt, Henry John, 1862-1938.
May 12 & 31, 1925
Osborn, Chase S. (Chase Salmon), b. 1860
July 16, 1909, Oct. 19, 1909, Nov. 15 & 30, 1909, Dec. 6 & 7, 1909, Feb. 3, 1910, Mar. 24, 1910, Apr. 7, 1910, May 23, 1910, June 10, 1910, Sept. 12, 1910, Nov. 16, 1910, Jan. 25, 1911, Oct. 3, 1911
Jan. 16, 1912, Mar. 11, 1912, Apr. 6, 1912, July 21 & 22, 1914, Nov. 16, 1914, May 17, 1915, Dec. 6, 1916, Apr. 20, 1917, Sept. 27, 1919, Dec. 31, 1925, Jan. 18, 1926, Apr. 8, 1926, July 26, 1926, Oct. 15, 1926
Jan. 10, 1927, July 22, 1929, Aug. 31, 1929, Jan. 22, 1931
Pattengill, Albert Henderson, 1842-1906.
May 28, 1903, Oct. 1, 1903
Perry, Stuart Hoffman, 1874-1957.
May 16, 1921, Nov. 29, 1921, Dec. 1, 1921, Dec. 9, 1921, Jan. 2, 1925
Phelps, William Lyon, 1865-1943.
Apr. 5, Apr. 11, 1916, Apr. 26, 1926, Jan. 11, 1927
Pipp, E. G.
Nov. 28, 1911, Dec. 22, 1911
Pound, Arthur, 1884-1966.
Jan. 4, 1909, Dec. 19, 1909, Mar. 10, 1913, Apr. 10, 1913, Apr. 12, 1913, May 20, 1913, May 17, 1916, Nov. 26, 1920, Oct. 27, 1921, May 20, 1924, June 24, 1924, Feb. 26, 1926, Oct. 27, 1926
Pound, Louise
Jan. 8 & 31, 1925, Feb. 15, 1925, Apr. 15, 1925, May 10 & 29, 1925, June 25, 1925, Aug. 1, 16 & 26, 1925
Rankin, Thomas E.
Oct. 9 & 24, 1923, Nov. 27, 1923, Dec. 13, 1923, Mar. 3, 1924, Apr. 8, 1924, May 6 & 20, 1924, June 3, 25 & 27, 1924, July 28, 1926, Aug. 26, 1926, Jan. 20, 1927, Jan. 7, 1928, Feb. 10, 1928, Dec. 16, 1928, May 26, 1929
Reed, Katherine
June 29, 1906, Sept. 22, 1907, Mar. 20, 1909
Schermerhorn, James.
Jan. 22, 1912
Scripps, James E. (James Edmund), 1835-1906.
July 8, 1904, Jan. 9, 1905
Shelley, Rebecca, 1887-1984.
Dec. 1, 1915
Slosson, Edwin Emery, 1865-1929.
Aug. 17, 1911, Dec. 18, 1911, Jan. 22, 1912, Feb. 23, 1912, Oct. 15, 1912, May 3 & 8, 1913, Mar. 2, 1914, Mar. 11 & 26, 1915
Slusser, Jean Paul
Nov. 11, 1909, Jan. 2, 1910, Feb. 13, 1910, Mar. 30, 1910, June 7, 1910, Sept. 3, 17 & 27, 1910, Apr. 23, 1912, Sept. 12, 14 & 29, 1912
Snyder, Alice D.
Nov. 3 & 14, 1922, Nov. 28, 1922, Jan. 21, 1923
Society for Pure English.
1922
Staebler, Neil, 1905-
Dec. 3, 1925
Stoddard, Francis Hovey, 1847-1936.
Jan. 18, 1891, Feb. 28, 1891, Mar. 21, 1906, Mar. 1909, Nov. 29, 1909, 1910
Taylor, Katherine
Sept. 11, 1909, Apr. 12, 1910, Apr. 12, 1910, Apr. 20, 1921, May 16, 1921
Thomas, Joseph M.
Sept. 20, 1909, Oct. 9 & 23, 1909, Nov. 8, 14 & 30, 1909, Dec. 29, 1909, Jan. 17, 1910, Feb. 4 & 11, 1910, Apr. 4 & 20, 1920, Oct. 23, 1911, Apr. 18 & 29, 1912, June 1, 1912, Sept. 30, 1912
Mar. 3 & 30, 1913, Apr. 23, 1913, May 6 & 19, 1913, Sept. 30, 1913, Apr. 17, 1914, May 12 & 18, 1914, Feb. 26, 1920, May 4, 1926, Nov. 26, 1926
Trueblood, Thomas C. (Thomas Clarkson), 1856-1951.
May 11, 1915
Wenley, R. M. (Robert Mark), 1861-1929.
Nov. 17, 1917, Nov. 22, 1923, Sept. 7, 1925
White, Lee A., b. 1886.
Oct. 3, 1911, Nov. 23, 1911, Dec. 3 & 10, 1911, Jan. 2, 1912, May 18, 1912, June 4, 1912, Sept. 22, 1912, Nov. 18, 1912, Dec. 15, 1912
Jan. 28, 1913, Feb. 10 & 24, 1913, Mar. 8, 1914, Apr. 16, 1914, May 7, 1914, Dec. 22, 1914
Feb. 26, 1915, May 28, 1915, Aug. 23, 1915, Oct. 9, 1915, Feb. 11, 1916, Mar. 11, 1916, May 16, 1916, Mar. 14, 1917, Apr. 3 & 13, 1917, May 13 & 15, 1917, July 25, 1917, Aug. 6, 14 & 24, 1917, Oct. 8 & 29, 1917, Nov. 7 & 30, 1917
Jan. 2 & 31, 1918, Apr. 9, 18 & 20, 1918, June 24 & 26, 1918, July 1, 7, 28 & 31, 1918, Sept. 16 & 19, 1918, Nov. 24, 1918, Dec. 13, 23 & 26, 1918
Jan. 17, 19 & 23, 1919, Feb. 11 & 18, 1919, Mar. 4, 5, 20 & 21, 1919, Apr. 1 & 25, 1919, May 1, 1919, July 6, 10, 18, 22, 25 & 26, 1919
Jan. 9, 1920, Jan. 9, 1920, Jan. 7, 1921, Mar. 3, 1921, Oct. 31, 1921, Nov. 8 & 15, 1921